It's 3am. Something's broken.
You want an AI agent to triage it.
But would you let one loose on your production systems?
Leavitt reads your dashboards the way an on-call engineer does.
Metrics, logs, client load, what just deployed.
It correlates them and tells you what broke.
And it physically cannot touch the thing it's watching.
It's a state machine. Every step is checked against the graph before it runs.
And the graph only knows how to read.
Diagnosis with no off-switch to flip.
Here it is on a real incident.
It finds the failing service, names the flag that caused it,
traces the cascade through frontend and checkout, and backs it all with evidence.
It runs headless. Nemotron on Crusoe drives it through the Hermes harness.
The model layer routes through TrueFoundry's gateway,
so when a provider browns out, the investigation fails over and keeps going.
Wire it to your alerts and this is what a shift looks like.
Webhook in, agent runs, report out.
Every step on the record.
Twenty-five runs a day, zero confident-wrong.
Here is what happens when the data lies.
Kill a source, feed it garbage.
A bare agent gets confident and wrong.
Leavitt degrades, or says inconclusive,
and it never once invents a cause it can't support.
Every investigation is on the record. Nothing it did is a mystery.
It only reads, so you can point it at production and walk away.
Leave it to Leavitt.